This is the new Paradise Sportswear Collection, the Cosmic Collection, and I think it's way too good for just a gym.
And I love it, so I'm going to style it today with some tights and I'm going to show it to you. Let's go!
Alright, I'm starting with the bodysuit. I've shown you the leggings in the intro, but the collection consists of several different pieces of bodysuits.
Long leggings in black and blue.
we have oh this is the other bodysuit I'm going to show you later
it's so confusing we have a bra and we have a jacket
but I think this is a nice piece also with the crisscross back here and what I immediately
noticed when I tried it on for the first time is that it's really long and I love that because as
you know I'm with my 172 centimeters meters 172 centimeters I'm quite tall my upper body is really
rather long so most of the bodysuits are too short on me and feel too short but this one
is so comfy and it feels so long and stretchy and I basically love this as a look you could
also wear it as like a swimsuit and not just for the gym to be honest I don't know if I would wear
it for the gym anyway because it might feel a bit uncomfortable for me personally with this bag
but I think it's a great outfit piece let me put the leggings on too because I think
this is going to work really nice together all right this is the combination with the leggings
This is the cosmic blue, the other color is black as I already showed you.
And for the bodysuit, for the bra part, there is padding inside.
So you have a slight push up effect and also it's way more comfortable this way you don't
need a bra because you have a built in bra which I really love.
So I kinda like the combination together.
It's the first time I'm wearing both pieces and I have to say it's not too much.
No.
Also today Paradise launched a completely new collection.
This one is already a few weeks old.
But they released new rainbow snake colors.
Pink, turquoise and light blue and white.
So you should check them out too.
With my code Celine you get 10% off.
I switched into the black set.
and I'm wearing the sports bra now of course there's also the bodysuit in black
and I can imagine that it is a bit less shiny reflective than the blue one so let me get more
light and I hope now there's better shine on the black clothes okay I'm going to put that away again
Anyway, if I'm being honest, I've never worn this collection to the gym and the black stuff was already released I think last year.
So I own these leggings and the sports bra also shorts for quite a while already.
I've worn it on holiday and daily life.
I love to wear them for the office because it's not, it doesn't look like sports leggings.
But it's really really comfy.
I've worn it for a long time, car drives, but never to the gym because I don't know, I don't feel like it's a gym wear outfit.
It looks too good.
One last piece for this collection, which is the jacket, also available in blue.
And it's the perfect match, of course, to the leggings, the bra and the bodysuit.
we have thumb holes here I love them and the jacket is version 2.0 so to say because they
also released a jacket last year but this is the new jacket it's longer which I love
because as a tall person I like that the jacket overlaps with the pants
and I don't get cold here
and all together like with the long sleeves and the long leggings it's a very very sleek
complete look take it if I close the zipper now it always looks like a catsuit
anyway I can so highly recommend this collection because it's just so comfy and it looks so great
and yeah whatever if you go to the gym or not give it a try use my discount code
and I will see you in the next video have a nice day bye